sign: TOMB RAIDER KING
Kyungtae: Die, you bastard!
Thug 2: B-Boss!
Thug 1: Boss!
Jooheon: I'll take good care of this.
Kyungtae: But... it's mine.
Jooheon: Let me show you
Jooheon: how you properly use it.
Thug 2: H-He stabbed me!
Jooheon: Well? Want to keep going?
Kyungjoo: What did you just say?!
sign: XIANG GALLERY
Kyungjoo: Jooheon Suh beat you up?
Kyungjoo: And then he did what?
Kyungjoo: You expect me to believe that?
Kyungtae: It's like he was possessed!
Kyungtae: He just came at us with some crazy moves!
Kyungtae: You should've seen the look in his eyes!
Kyungtae: How much did he take from you?
Kyungtae: All the money in my account
and... the Buddha statue.
Kyungjoo: What?!
Kyungjoo: You useless little shit!
Kyungjoo: Go get it back right now, idiot!
Jooheon: Hm, strange.
Pawnbroker: That thing isn't even worth fifty bucks.
Pawnbroker: Might as well get rid of it.
Jooheon: It can't just be junk if Kyungtae
held on to it that tightly.
sign: SPY SKILL ACTIVATED
THE STATUE CONTAINS A SUSPICIOUS SUBSTANCE.
Jooheon: A suspicious substance?
Jooheon: Don't tell me....
Jooheon: Of course.
Jooheon: Well, look at that.
Jooheon: That’s nothing you'd
hand over to a pawnshop.
Geonwoo: Hey, Jooheon?
Jooheon: Hi, Geonwoo.
sign: XIANG GALLERY
Kyungjoo: I-I am terribly sorry.
Kyungjoo: Yes, sir.
Kyungjoo: Of course, I truly am...
Kyungjoo: Who is it? I'm on the phone!
Kyungtae: K-Kyungjoo.
Geonwoo: We received a tip
about several drug offenses.
Kyungjoo: D-Drugs? We're law-abiding citizens!
Kyungjoo: All we sell is art.
Geonwoo: We already collected the evidence.
I assume the rest is in the warehouse?
Kyungjoo: They even know about
the warehouse in Gyeonggi-do?
Kyungjoo: Good thing every room
is password protected.
Kyungjoo: A warehouse? And what evidence?
Kyungjoo: Even the police cannot just...
Policeman: All 600 pieces of art have been checked!
Policeman: We found drugs in all of them.
Kyungjoo: Y-You... opened all the rooms?!
Detective: Nice and quiet now.
Kyungjoo: But every room had
a different password. How?
Geonwoo: One moment, ma'am.
Geonwoo: For you.
Jooheon: Maybe you should've
lived a little more decently.
Kyungjoo: N-No … Jooheon Suh?
Jooheon: Passwords need to be changed
every now and then, you know?
Jooheon: Well... enjoy prison.
Kyungjoo: You filthy little rat!
Kyungjoo: I'll kill you for this!
sign: GEONWOO
sign: YOU’LL GET YOUR
100 MILLION WON REWARD SOON.
sign: DON’T BLOW IT ALL
AND SAVE THE MONEY!
Geonwoo: You'll get your 100
million won reward soon.
Geonwoo: Don't blow it all and save the money!
Jooheon: He worries way too much.
Jooheon: That takes care of my starting capital.
Jooheon: First, I'll get some sleep.
Jooheon: Then tomorrow, the tomb hunt begins.
Jooheon: What the? Where's my apartment?
Jooheon: Did a tomb... appear here?
Jooheon: Is this good or bad luck?
Citizen 1: Yeah, it's unbelievable.
Citizen 2: How is this possible?
Linda: Yes, I just arrived.
Linda: Korea doesn't know
about the tombs yet, correct?
Linda: We'll be detonating this one soon.
Linda: Yes. So far, no one seems
to have recognized it as a tomb.
Linda: Understood.
Kiyoshi: Hello there.
Linda: You?
Kiyoshi: Why so surprised, Linda Walker?
Linda: What is the Japanese
excavation team doing here?
Kiyoshi: That’s hardly something
someone from the States should ask.
Kiyoshi: How's the jet lag?
Linda: So we're full-on thieves now, Abe?
Kiyoshi: Come on, we both know what
we're after. Why the hypocrisy?
Kiyoshi: Save your energy. The relic is ours.
Jooheon: Well, well.
Jooheon: The CIA and the Japanese
team are already here.
Jooheon: But what kind of amateur
would blow up a tomb?
Jooheon: Good. Looks like
there's no experts around.
Jooheon: Aren't these...
Jooheon: Yes, without a doubt – tomb glyphs.
Jooheon: The language of those damned relics.
Jooheon: The funny part is:
Jooheon: These relics go into great detail
writing about themselves.
Jooheon: If you can read the glyphs, you'll find
out where the entrance and traps are.
Jooheon: This is going great already.
Jooheon: Let's start reading, then.
sign: [EXPERT CRYPTOGRAPHER]
YOU HAVE GAINED A NEW TITLE AND UNLOCKED A SKILL.
sign: TOMB RAIDER BASIC SKILLS
LINGUISTICS (RANK F) HAS BEEN ACTIVATED.
Jooheon: Ha, how generous of that winged bastard.
sign: TOMB RAIDER BASIC SKILLS (2/4)
sign: SPY [RANK F]
DETECT EVERYTHING IN A 1 METER RADIUS
sign: LINGUISTICS [RANK F]
IMPROVED UNDERSTANDING WITH ALL LANGUAGES
Jooheon: Perfect. Only two skills left.
Jooheon: This should be the place.
Jooheon: All right, let's go!
Kiyoshi: What is that?
CIA Agent: The tomb entrance seems to be opening!
Linda: What? It's opening?
Kiyoshi: What a spectacle!
Linda: How is this happening?
Jooheon: Something should be
showing up around here by now.
Jooheon: Ah.
Jooheon: This is the right place.
Jooheon: Found it.
Jooheon: Hm. This should do it.
Snake: Oh, a visitor.
Snake: Yet another poor soul
has dropped his treasure.
Snake: Speak.
Jooheon: Hey, over here!
Jooheon: Can't you see me?
Snake: Hm?
Snake: You blind old serpent!
Snake: Now, then...
Snake: The gold knife or the silver knife.
Which one is yours?
Jooheon: This relic is based on
"The Gold Axe and the Silver Axe".
Jooheon: A very famous story that originates
from one of Aesop's fables,
Jooheon: with variations found all over the world.
Jooheon: Even foreigners can
clear this tomb easily.
Jooheon: But this time, it's my turn first.
Snake: I await your answer.
Jooheon: Unfortunately, neither one is mine.
Snake: Oh-ho. An honest human.
Snake: Then perhaps this one belongs to you?
Jooheon: You bet it does.
Jooheon: If I say yes, I get my knife,
a gold axe, and a silver axe.
Jooheon: That would clear the tomb.
Jooheon: But...
Jooheon: May I take a closer look at it?
Snake: Of course.
Snake: What do you think you're doing?!
Jooheon: Shut up. I don't trust you things.
Jooheon: There's no guarantee
you'll reward me fairly.
Jooheon: Your gift could easily turn me
Jooheon: into a deranged murderer.
Snake: H-How do you know about that, human?
Jooheon: I think it happened in the US back then.
sign: SERIAL KILLINGS IN THE STATES
sign: RELIC USER CAUSES YET ANOTHER TRAGEDY
Jooheon: At the time, the axe relic
Jooheon: turned its user into a serial killer.
Jooheon: This is your end.
Jooheon: So...
Jooheon: submit already, relic!
Snake: So this is how you plan to claim me?
Jooheon: Let's see how strong you are.
Jooheon: I'll use "dominance" to subdue you!
Jooheon: Affinity: The ability
to control relics through trust.
Jooheon: Dominance – the ability
to coerce and force a relic to obey.
Jooheon: And compatibility.
Jooheon: The ideal bond between relic and master.
Jooheon: Like a musician with an instrument relic.
Jooheon: You... stubborn worm!
Snake: Away! Begone!
Jooheon: I'm not going to suck up to you relics!
Jooheon: I don't give a damn
about affinity this time round.
Jooheon: Obey me, relic!
Jooheon: Or I'll destroy you.
Jooheon: Do you think I won't do it?!
Snake: Enough, you lunatic!
Jooheon: What a pest.
Jooheon: You should've obeyed from the start.
Jooheon: Will you look at that shine.
sign: [TOMB SURVIVOR]
YOU HAVE GAINED A NEW TITLE AND UNLOCKED A SKILL.
sign: TOMB RAIDER BASIC SKILLS
TOMB EXCAVATION [RANK F] HAS BEEN ACTIVATED.
sign: TOMB RAIDER BASIC SKILLS (3/4)
sign: SPY [RANK F]
DETECT EVERYTHING IN A 1 METER RADIUS
sign: LINGUISTICS [RANK F]
IMPROVED UNDERSTANDING WITH ALL LANGUAGES
sign: TOMB EXCAVATION [RANK F]
INCREASED UNDERSTANDING OF TOMBS
Jooheon: Oh, a new skill.
Jooheon: Only one more left.
How should I unlock it?
sign: [ABUSER OF RELICS]
sign: YOU HAVE ACQUIRED A NEW TITLE.
YOUR DOMINANCE HAS INCREASED.
sign: YOUR AFFINITY HAS DECREASED.
Jooheon: "Abuser of Relics"?
Jooheon: "Abuser" of all things, hah.
Jooheon: You damn crow,
Jooheon: you're trying to mess with me, aren't you?
Kiyoshi: It should be right ahead...
Kiyoshi: There's the pond!
Kiyoshi: Just as the prophecy foretold.
Kiyoshi: Come on out, relic.
Linda: W-What are you doing?
Jooheon: You idiots are too late.
Kiyoshi: Why is nothing happening?
Kiyoshi: The prophet said all I needed to do
was throw a relic in the pond!
Linda: A prophet?
Linda: So Japan really does
have a prophecy relic.
Kiyoshi: N-No! Stop trying to get intel from me!
Kiyoshi: What's going on now?
Linda: A-An earthquake.
Kiyoshi: Damn it, something's wrong!
Kiyoshi: We have to get out!
sign: XIANG GALLERY
Seungwoo: Damn it!
Seungwoo: They really took everything.
Thug 1: With both of our bosses arrested
this business is finished …
Seungwoo: I'm aware, dumbass.
Seungwoo: And it's all Jooheon Suh's fault.
Seungwoo: But this isn't over.
Thug 2: Yeah, that’s more like it!
Are you gonna kick his ass?
Seungwoo: Duh! Nobody gets away from me.
Seungwoo: Or else I wouldn't be Seungwoo Oh!
Thug 1: Wow!
Thug 2: Wow!
sign: INCOMING CALL
sign: ERRAND BOY JOOHEON SUH
sign: DECLINE  ACCEPT
Seungwoo: Oh?
Seungwoo: Y-Yeah? Hello?
Jooheon: What took you so long?
Do you have a death wish?
Seungwoo: W-Where's your respect, huh?
Jooheon: Yeah, yeah.
Jooheon: You guys need to run
a little errand for me.
Kiyoshi: That was a total failure.
Kiyoshi: Hm? There was another prophecy?
Director of JSDF: A Korean beat us to it.
We only just found out.
Kiyoshi: And you kept that from me?!
Director of JSDF: You know what that relic user is like.
Kiyoshi: Don't tell me
Kiyoshi: she couldn't read the kanji again.
Director of JSDF: Well, kids these days.
Director of JSDF: We're working on it.
So you keep doing your best too.
Director of JSDF: And be careful of that Korean.
Kiyoshi: W-What? Why?
Director of JSDF: The prophecy was rather grim.
Director of JSDF: He's called
"the one who will devour the world."
Seungwoo: What? Midas?!
Jooheon: Midas is the world's
largest secret auction house
Jooheon: based in Las Vegas.
Jooheon: If I keep an eye on what's going on there,
I might learn what Kwon is planning.
Jooheon: Go to this month's auction
to find a few items and a person for me.
Jooheon: Look for Jack Kayman, also known as JK.
Jooheon: That's his alias.
Seungwoo: Don't be ridiculous!
How are we supposed to get in there?
Jooheon: Figure that out yourselves.
Jooheon: I'll pay well,
so expenses won't be an issue.
Jooheon: I won't be forcing you, of course.
Jooheon: You do have a choice:
Jooheon: Go willingly, or I'll beat you there.
Worker: Goodbye!
Jooheon: Good. That should cover
the preparations for now.
Jooheon: Time to go relic hunting.
Newscaster: Breaking news.
Newscaster: This marks the fourth murder
reported this month.
Newscaster: The suspect allegedly attempted
suicide by self-immolation.
sign: SUICIDE ATTEMPT NEAR YEONGDEUNGPO STATION
Newscaster: According to witnesses...
Jooheon: Just like how it was back then,
before a new tomb appeared.
Kiyoshi: Hey! Watch where you're going!
Jooheon: Oh? That’s the guy I locked in the tomb.
Jooheon: If he's here, then
Kiyoshi: How about an apology?
Jooheon: the next tomb must be appearing soon.
Jooheon: Around this time,
someone in Japan had a prophecy relic.
Kiyoshi: What are you staring at?
Jooheon: And it looks like this guy
also has a relic on him.
Jooheon: That dumbass isn't even hiding its aura.
Kiyoshi: Something wrong with your head?
Jooheon: Whatever it is, I want it.
Kiyoshi: Hey!
Kiyoshi: Are you even listening to me?!
Kiyoshi: What the hell?!
Jooheon: Oh, I'm terribly sorry.
Kiyoshi: It's all over my clothes!
Kiyoshi: You better pay for dry cleaning!
This is expensive!
Jooheon: Sadly, I don't have any money.
Jooheon: It doesn't look expensive anyway.
Kiyoshi: Excuse me?
sign: JAPANESE EXCAVATION TEAM
Jooheon: You dropped your ID.
Kiyoshi: G-Give that to me!
Kiyoshi: Did he recognize me?
Kiyoshi: No one can know that the JSDF is in Korea.
Jooheon: Bingo! A tomb manifestation.
Jooheon: A new one is appearing right now.
Kiyoshi: Good. Just like the prophecy.
Kiyoshi: Hello? The manifestation has just begun.
Director of JSDF: I know. We also received a prophecy
Director of JSDF: that the Korean with
the axe relic is near you.
Director of JSDF: And that you, for some reason,
Director of JSDF: should be careful around alcohol.
Kiyoshi: That little shit
Kiyoshi: was the guy from the prophecy?